export const affiliateData = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "How do I become an affiliate with ExpertSkillz?",
    answer:
      'Becoming an ExpertSkillz affiliate is simple and stress-free. Simply click Become an Affiliate to pay a one-time subscription fee. After payment, you will be redirected to Sign Up to create and fully activate your account.',
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "How often do affiliates get paid?",
    answer:
      "Affiliates receive payments every week for their affiliate commissions.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "In what currency are affiliate payments made?",
    answer:
      "Affiliate payments are made in US dollars (USD). However, affiliates can withdraw their earnings to their local currency.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Do affiliates need to pay anything to get started?",
    answer:
      "Apart from the one-time subscription fee, ExpertSkillz provides all the necessary resources and tools for affiliates to begin their affiliate marketing without any further costs.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What support is available for affiliates?",
    answer:
      "ExpertSkillz offers dedicated support to affiliates, assisting them with any questions or issues they may encounter during their affiliate journey.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Can affiliates track their earnings and performance?",
    answer:
      "Yes, affiliates have access to a dashboard where they can track their earnings, performance metrics, and other relevant data in real-time.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Are there any minimum requirements to become an affiliate?",
    answer:
      "There are no specific minimum requirements to become an affiliate with ExpertSkillz. We welcome individuals from all backgrounds and levels of experience to join our affiliate program.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "How can affiliates promote ExpertSkillz courses?",
    answer:
      "Affiliates are provided with various marketing materials, including flyers, and promotional content, to effectively promote ExpertSkillz courses to their audience.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "When do affiliates get paid?",
    answer:
      "Affiliates can withdraw their earnings every Saturday, the only day designated for withdrawals. Once withdrawn, funds are allocated to your local bank account on Sunday.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "How can affiliates contact support for assistance?",
    answer:
      "Affiliates can reach out to our support team via email or through the support portal for any inquiries or assistance needed regarding their affiliate activities.",
    open: false,
  },
];
